I was stupid in my last video five early
signs of a garbage anime protagonist I
said hey if this gets 15,000 likes I
will upload five early signs of a
garbage anime villain within a week of
it hitting 15,000 likes well apparently
you guys liked it I don't know a fifteen
thousand likes right away so here you go
from five early signs of a garbage anime
villain this is a completely educational
non meme whatsoever our video that is
purely to help you in your quest to
picking out absolutely trash enemy
villains right from the start you'll
find it's much easier than you think
after you see these five clauses that
are nearly invisible to the naked eye
that once elucidated will shine forth on
some how most two enemy villains but
that's not the point the point is this
is purely as a public service video to
help and not to completely just mask
this as an excuse to sarcastically
insult anime villains or a thinly veiled
excuse to crap over anime not for any
particular reason aside from the fact
that it's a hell of a lot of fun okay
good well it's time to up the ante when
this video hits 20,000 likes within a
week from hitting that or perhaps
earlier if I never hit that I will be
making a video 5 early signs of a
garbage anime fight and I actually think
that's gonna be a pretty dope one so
like away fanbase and let us begin with
early sign of a garbage villain number 1
as you are all aware before meeting the
main villain ever you always end up
meeting his army of cronies because what
villain can properly do anything without
an army of cronies II you get what I'm
saying
now the sign that it's a garbage villain
is simply due to what the cronies add to
the story first and foremost if there's
a number of cronies that's a bad sign
the 9 Akatsuki the seven sins of
purgatory the Arashi on six the nine
gates of hell the 10 Espada the 13
members of the phantom troupe the 10
commandments the seven homunculus the
sense we 7 if the villain group tells
you the amount of villains in the group
in the name of the group well then I
can't commend the leadership skills of
whoever's running the thing it's like
this
each group of several people that
operates in the shadows and they're all
badass and they're so badass and secrets
in fact we're gonna tell you exactly how
many of them there are so they can match
up exactly equally to all of the main
characters that fight them they all lose
one-on-one fights and then the main
character takes down the main bad guy I
see this as relatively counter
production in the art of stealth and it
does not bode well if the main villain
thinks it's a pretty wacky cool idea to
put a number in the title of his group
but in any case that's not the only
thing we can see from the cronies you
can immediately tell if there's a little
bit wrong fishy with the melon if you
know they end up fighting the guys in
the group one at a time or at least in
pairs or whatever the hell obviously the
number in the group is to scare everyone
else because each of them is so powerful
in fact more often than not on an
individual level a single member from
one of these groups should be able to
take out throngs of good guys well
imagine putting them all together one
place the main villain is so smart in
stealthy that'll only send them one at a
time Power Rangers style to defeat the
good guys and honestly they're defeated
by teamwork and stuff so great plan
their main bad guy then the main bad guy
secretly is more powerful than all of
them put together so he didn't really
need them which begs the question why he
originally had at them and that's
because he didn't want to get his hands
muddied in the dirty work of the world
shut up main bad guy if you're sending
out your cronies individually to die but
it doesn't actually bother you because
you're secretly way stronger than all of
them put together for shame I mean
literally I don't know what's going
through the guy's head for the same
exact price he could have been a
relatively good guy still be overpowered
and then by default amass a harem of
anime whamon by his sides to defeat the
forces of evil but there's more that you
can learn about the cronies more often
than not if the cronies around purely to
hype the abilities of the main bad guy
then you didn't really need the chrony
there at all and he was just their type
the main bad guy further this main bad
guy is walking around with a hype squad
a literal group of elite doofuses to
purely flex on the haters I mean in like
the seven deadly sins when Goliath first
fought the sins the sins power level
averaged at around 3,000 each and you
land at a power level of like 26,000 he
completely obliterated them and then of
course he was secretly
the weakest of the 10 commandments all
along and then every sin manages to get
crazy power boosts way over power all of
them and bam demon king five hundred
thousand power level yeah Goliath was
really helpful wasn't he or you have
someone like Aizen and bleach and his
epic group of Espada each with a number
ranking them and power from lowest to
highest and then he kind of just left a
bunch of them in hueco mundo to die off
fighting some of the captains that were
there while he invaded the human world
now if he's already raking them
consecutively from weakest to strongest
and they're fighting them taking them
down one at a time of course none of the
Espada thought it was a good idea to
team up against the Soul Reapers but hey
I'm not the tactical mastermind here and
it's not even that Aizen was stupid in
this regard aizen's a freaking genius he
didn't need the Espada they were just
kind of there to make the fights cooler
he could have just invaded the human
world with his entire group of Espada
and then oh my god ichigo byakuya
kampachi and all the other guys that
were there are gonna be trapped in hueco
mundo until they find a way out well
everyone is on his side to deal with
them but no they're just too flexed so
therefore it's much cooler if they have
individual fights so that is side one of
a potentially garbage anime villain keep
an eye on the cronies but now let's get
into the meat and potatoes of the man
himself I don't see man to some sexist
they say man because there are very few
enemy whamming that are actually main
villains too if the main villain is
actually an enemy whamon now not trying
to insult anyone here by saying this but
let's be frank I made a list of the top
10 anime villains and they also had like
20 honorable mentions not gonna lie
don't think any were whamon which is
very sad gender equality is extremely
important and must be stressed so
therefore I think it's crucial to say
that anime whamon should have the right
to be amazing villains as well but
they're not they're like oh here's an
epic anime whamon villain Kaguya yeah
that's right literally farted out of
Kishimoto z-- but just because he didn't
want modern to be the main villain or
something early signs of a garbage anime
villain if they pop out of nowhere with
zero hype but secretly
they're the alien goddess overpowered
creature that will take over the planet
with their insane abilities and shiz but
of course there is one exception to this
an exception where an anime villain can
actually be both good and
Waymon and that is if they were secretly
in love with the main character and it
doesn't even need to be so secret the
main villain andrey creators as well as
s death from a cameo kill show that with
spades strong women loving the main
character or something along those lines
so it's not that we have no epic anime
villain whamon but it's usually a
telltale sign that it's not gonna be the
most wonderful villain on the face of
the planet
not trying to be sexist here or anything
I am just once again advocating gender
equality saying that women have the
right to be terribly horrible anime
villains as well and I want to see women
being destroyed by the main characters
and extremely brutal ways that didn't
come out right
anyway moving on sign number three and
once again this is a bit of a
conglomerate early sign of a garbage
anime villain and it's anything that
involves building up the villains
ideology so now there are some really
epic villains really cool psychologies
and ideology but unfortunately the vast
majority do not fall under those exact
guidelines if the main villain is
actually related to the main character
because he was either trained by the
same master or he was the master or he
was the wayward student or he was his
father or his uncle or his stepbrothers
pet goat you know there's a problem you
have this massive world with this
probably underdog protagonist that's
gonna try to claw his way up from the
very bottom where no one expected
anything of him surprise the main
villain all along is literally just like
him to some degree let's look at some
villains in Naruto pain trained by the
same master Madara from the same clan as
the other main character there we go we
got both main characters to have their
step cousins attempt world domination
lovely who's the main villain in the
seven deadly sins well is it Mele Otis's
father what that's like the craziest
coincidence ever but it gets better why
did the villain become evil this is
again part of the upbringing and an
early sign of a garbage anime villain as
if his reasoning to go off the hinges
off the wall nutso is not exactly
something that would befall most people
in their exact situations once again
let's look at Naruto for a moment
Payne's friend died so because that's
very sad he decided world domination
Audra was just a humble dude that didn't
feel like the UGA clan were being
treated fairly in the Lee village world
domination Thai boys
Obito sacrificed himself for his friend
for the good of the world and then it
turns out that the person that he wanted
to save most ended up dying
well did his uh his wife who just died
well in I think that calls for world
domination ladies and gentlemen world
domination in general is a bad sign it's
a way to say the universe effed you so
it's time to eff the universe and it's
not exactly a logic that most of us
follow
I lied that's a logic that way too many
of us follow unfortunately but it
shouldn't be but now it doesn't only
apply to villains that decided they
wanted to take over the world because
that one time they stubbed their toe is
way too painful and it forced them to
become evil and they have some crazy
reasoning as to why that works out but
it applies to any villain who has that
exact same ideology you have some dope
villains like staying from my hero
academia due to this powerful ideology
that caused his view of the world to
warp into something different he had a
different view of what makes a hero he
followed this path of his with such an
intense passion his pure willpower alone
was enough to terrify the heroes
detaining him after he was defeated that
is a powerful ideology for a villain
it's a great reason for him to do what
he's doing not to say that I fully agree
and can condone the idea of killing good
people because they're not good for the
right reasons not exactly what I'm
trying to push here fam but then you
compare him to other villains in the
series like I don't know
Tamura Palmer is a pretty great villain
and uh that's all lovely but ask him his
motivations and it might give you a
telltale sign of what he's willing to
become so tomorrow what do you want to
do well I wouldn't kill all might
because he's good and I'm evil Wow Tomer
are very cool but uh
all-4-one was the guy training you what
does he plan on doing oh he just wants
to destroy the world or take it over or
make evil reign supreme or whatever very
epic ideologies right here fan and it's
not at all an early sign of a garbage
villain because that's not what this
video is this video is not pointing at
specific villains saying why they're
garbage but if they're evil for the sake
of evil or if they want to take over the
world because they want to take over the
world not a good sign at all unless it's
rider from fate/zero he has full rights
who wants to take over the world and not
only do I approve of
actions but I condoned them if you are
like Ryder you too deserve to take over
the world and cause world domination but
not because you're evil for the sake of
evil evil for the sake of evil is bad so
Kaguya showing up last minute is trying
to wipe everything out hmm
if you ask the demon king from seven
deadly sins yo demon king why are you
making such a mess trying to destroy
everyone and the answers because I'm the
demon king you know that is not a good
sign you gotta take the Scooby Doo
approach a little bit in scooby Doo
every single episode the gang who goes
to some new place and there's some masks
to l'm going as destroying shoes or
whatever the hell he decides to be doing
now you have a ton of characters in the
series you have the evil hermit
that's tries to get visitors away you
have the extremely rich guy that's
trying to take over the land
you have the angry hobo with anger
management issues and you have Steve
your regular nice guy that invites them
in and buys them coffee well the bad
guys gonna be Steve I know pretty
mind-blowing right the rest is just like
evil for the sake of evil not Steve
Steve avoids that entire problem and is
one of the greatest villains in all of
anime in fact he would have probably
even gotten away with it too if it
wasn't for those meddling kids and that
dumb dog but sometimes they do have
crazy cool ideologies a crazy cool
psychology backing up what they're doing
however even so that does not completely
save them this is an early sign of a
garbage annum evil a terrible ideology a
horrible psychology evil for the sake of
evil bad motives yes but even with all
the right motives and even with no hype
and not necessarily related to the main
character if everything was part of
their plan sorry fam that is not how it
works and I do not relate to you except
for Aizen you're amazing and I do relate
to you I made a whole video on Aizen
he's amazing check it out not the point
if everything was secretly part of your
evil plan then nothing was I don't think
that's how that line works but we're
gonna go with it anyway hahaha I knew
you would take three steps forward on
this very day and I have planned this
trap 14 years ago expecting your arrival
right now but how do you know because I
dyed it every moment in your life making
you just as strong as you are now so
that you could be here taking these
three steps and I am very cool but
but how is that possible silence I do
not need to answer questions from you
fools not a good sign for an enemy
villain want to know a way better
approach to the exact same scenario but
changes it all into a much better light
I have planned out your entire life
since your very birth knowing that you
would take these 3 steps exactly right
now here today at this exact power level
you're at because they pitted every
opponent against you to make you just as
strong as you could possibly be to have
the most epic fight against me where you
just barely win and then when the main
character says how did you know if you
would have gone with the generic silence
fool or because I am very cool answer
not a good sign for a villain but he
would say oh how did I know because it's
me do that is top to your signs of an
enemy village and I know that's not
exactly what this video was supposed to
be but I just had to talk about a very
easy way to get out of the entire
situation and if you really want to add
some spice when the main villain says so
he planned out your entire life the good
guys supposed to say Nami and then the
bad guy could skip right to what does
you uh do this and then you know it
evolves into an epic battle but not
every anime is JoJo's and I understand
why not every anime is amazing to that
degree of writing however if he planned
out your entire life and he's not gonna
give you a logical way how he did it not
a great sign of a villain black zetsu
screw yourself and as far as the fifth
and final early sign of a garbage anime
villain their powers I know this sounds
generic and very surface level stuff I'm
skipping all the themes not talking
about any of the philosophy of the
series no psychology no ideology no
astrophysics or whatever the hell else I
talk about in my analysis videos where I
make believe I'm smart and whatever no
fewer basic powers if the guy could drop
a meteor that's actually really cool so
I'm gonna give him either a pass on that
one but if you're a guy like lark aid
from Fairy Tail or in fact speaking of
Fairy Tail let's use that as a prime
example of this one I don't want to go
far off topic here but some powers are
so broken it doesn't make sense how
they're defeated and it's not like I
want to make fun of Fairy Tail or
anything here it's not exactly what I'm
being paid for but it's a prime example
as far as this bryggen 12 when the power
levels get out of control Larke aid
dragged Neil from Fairy Tail is part of
this bryggen 12 this extremely
overpowered enemy organization and you
know immediately that there's an issue
because this brigand 12 just there
hi bubs Arif very cool fairytale again
not the point
I think that enemy got the point lark
AIDS abilities include you know having
everyone within a certain radius of him
go into such major orgasms that they
cannot seem to fight that is correct
of course he immediately runs into
battle against like three whamon and all
three of those women all of a sudden
start squealing and breathing heavy and
they fall on the ground and they're
touching themselves in weird places and
Mark aid is one of the greatest villains
in anime I take that all back his other
incredible moves include making everyone
around him suffer from hunger so since
they're hungry all the anime characters
around him
mostly ramen as we've already
established start licking each other and
chewing on each other and taking off
each others clothes to bite each other
in better place I don't know where Kate
is one of the greatest villains of all
time what am I saying here I don't even
know how I'm insulting the guy and
you'll even notice a pretty funny trend
here one of these friggin twelve is this
assassin dude and he has the ability to
trap everyone around him into this
little pocket dimension that he holds in
his palm completely destroying them and
defeating them without even needing to
fight them no matter how powerful they
are no matter who they are
blammo yes he only does it once because
otherwise it would be crazy o P but
they're all trapped in little pocket
dimension since it's so overpowered and
ridiculously strong I don't see how
anyone can ever defeat him in fact I
think he might be able to defeat all of
Fairy Tail however he's extremely shy
and if he sees a ramen that is not fully
clothed he'll be too embarrassed to
fight close his eyes and the web and
will then defeat him spoilers Lucy was
completely naked and managed to teleport
right in front of him
epic win for Fairy Tail other crazy
overpowered characters from this bryggen
12 include this guy that can look into
all of the opponent's memories or even
his friends memories and every foe that
they've ever fought is now reese
summoned back maybe not at their full
power but at most of their power that
they would have to fight them again so
that means even though a bunch of this
bryggen 12 are actually defeated he can
then re summon their memories from the
dead and they're basically as strong as
they were before and annihilating all
their progress probably one of the most
overpowered broken abilities ever that
most anime wouldn't even dare touch but
Fairy Tail is so epic they came up with
a villain it's so strong now uh this
villain decide to go hand-to-hand fight
some opponents and not unite
yeah and the hand fights with the guy
who has the most overpowered ability
every and to just sit in his castle
making an endless army of foes they've
already defeated constantly revive and
continue to fight them very cool but the
problem isn't even that he had to fight
them hand-to-hand because we know that
he had to be defeated eventually the
power is once you introduce any ability
so strong there's no way you could get
around it like Irene for example from
fairytale versus mother crazy powerful
wizard one of this friggin twelve one of
the three strongest to this bryggen
twelve in fact she used a single move
that rearranged the entire continent
they were standing on to destroy the
enemy battle lines and to get certain
people in different places now if you
want to talk Opie broken abilities you
don't get much more than that she did it
with the snap of the fingers how
ridiculous is that well unfortunately
she was in the range of lark aide who
caused her to start orgasming so she
couldn't really continue the fight and
she had to retreat for now Wow now I'm
not making this an excuse to bag on
fairy tale I just feel like the spring
in 12 were built to be so overpowered
with such wacky abilities all of them
really have the potential to be an
absolutely trash atom even they're not
saying that they are I'm just saying
these characteristics are sometimes
telling I mean there's the woman that
can trap everyone in Tsavo stop time
walk up to them and stop time and
annihilate them but Natsu was so strong
he was able to lay time on fire and
defeat her yeah anime logic 101 don't
make the villain too overpowered with
such broken abilities that it doesn't
make any sense how they're defeated one
of the early signs for a garbage villain
is if the ability is that broken but
again this is not to bag on fairy tale
at the end of seven at least in season
one which is a series that I actually do
like a lot just like fairy tale being
that I'm one of the few anime youtubers
that praises Fairy Tail for the things
that does well hendrickson gets gray
demon abilities and of course gray
demons end up completely useless in the
scheme of things
but with his great demon ability he
manages to use this black snow thing go
that anyone that comes in contact with
this black powder thing automatically
dies yes that is a very broken power no
he does not use it on the seven deadly
sins he only does it on nameless
characters that die and it's like we
don't really care but it actually hits
Hawk the pig the mascot of the series
Hauk dies this is so sad good news is
Elizabeth managed to unlock a power that
can bring everyone dead back to life yes
Elizabeth
that ridiculous powerup of yours
actually was not your fault it was
because of the stupidly broken power of
the anime villain net not only do we
never see anyone else use this black
snow powder thing again even though
Hendrickson's power level at that point
was like highballing 5000 and the demon
Kang's is like five hundred thousand but
Elizabeth never uses this revive from
the dead thing go again either I mean
you just can't win with stupid powers
unless your fairy tale because most of
them managed to get a whamon naked
somehow and that definitely tips the
scales to fairytales favor in the
writing of brilliant anime villains with
brilliant powers I hope you did enjoy
this video hope you learned something
new and can broaden your horizons for
the future sharpening your mind with
pure facts and no memes and I hope you
could take satire because if not that
was prolly terrible subscribe if you
enjoyed 20,000 likes and you get 5 early
signs of a garbage anime fight within
the week and remember to stay weird BAM
[Music]